<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>information security on Catscrdl</title>
    <link>https://catscrdl.io/tags/information-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in information security on Catscrdl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://catscrdl.io/tags/information-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Detection as Code: A Maturity Framework</title>
      <link>https://catscrdl.io/blog/detectionascodematurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://catscrdl.io/blog/detectionascodematurity/</guid>
      <description>Detection as Code: A Maturity Framework Introduction In the ever-evolving landscape of cybersecurity, the methodologies and tools we rely on are continually advancing. One of the latest trends is Detection as Code (DaC), which promises to revolutionize threat detection by integrating software engineering practices into security operations. Having worked in an organization that practices DaC for several years, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to realize that it&amp;rsquo;s not simply a matter of whether or not to adopt DaC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There are Only Two Rules</title>
      <link>https://catscrdl.io/blog/thereareonlytworules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://catscrdl.io/blog/thereareonlytworules/</guid>
      <description>Intro In the field of detection engineering, understanding and applying the right frameworks is crucial for effectively identifying and responding to threats. Mental models provide a structured way of categorizing and approaching the myriad of security alerts and anomalies we face daily. These models help us dissect and understand the behavior of potential threats, allowing for a more targeted and effective defense strategy. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how I use one mental model to clearly classify every detection rule into one of two categories and how that helps shape the decision of what kind of detections I build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Resilient Detection Suppressions</title>
      <link>https://catscrdl.io/blog/buildingresilientsuppressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://catscrdl.io/blog/buildingresilientsuppressions/</guid>
      <description>Intro Raise your hand if you&amp;rsquo;ve worked on suppressing a false positive for a detector and then the very next day, it&amp;rsquo;s back in your &amp;ldquo;fix&amp;rdquo; queue with another false positive. I&amp;rsquo;d expect almost everyone who&amp;rsquo;s worked in detection engineering for any period of time has their hand raised or is nodding along. Why does this happen? Well, sometimes the detector itself isn&amp;rsquo;t very good and it&amp;rsquo;s alerting on a lot of benign behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Write an Actionable Alert</title>
      <link>https://catscrdl.io/blog/howtowriteanactionablealert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://catscrdl.io/blog/howtowriteanactionablealert/</guid>
      <description>Intro &amp;ldquo;If a tree falls in a forest and no one is around to hear it, does it make a sound?&amp;rdquo;
This mantra about possibly non-existent trees very much applies to detection engineers. If you write a great rule to detect malicious behavior, but no one (or nothing) acts upon the alert, did you really catch the threat actor? Or worse, an analyst acts on the alert but responds incorrectly. In this article, I will cover the importance of not only writing solid detections, but also solid alerts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>