<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Demo on Daniel Wyleczuk-Stern</title>
    <link>https://daniel-infosec.github.io/tags/demo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Demo on Daniel Wyleczuk-Stern</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daniel-infosec.github.io/tags/demo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source SaaS Reconnaissance Utilizing Subdomains</title>
      <link>https://daniel-infosec.github.io/blog/opensourcesubdomainrecon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daniel-infosec.github.io/blog/opensourcesubdomainrecon/</guid>
      <description>On a recent Purple Team engagement, I was accessing the client&amp;rsquo;s Splunk cloud instance. Being my normal typo-filled self, I fat fingered the URL and went to clieent.splunkcloud.com instead of the appropraite client.splunkcloud.com. Instead of being redirected to the login portal, I received a DNS resolution error, fixed the typo, and moved on. A little while later, I was thinking about the typo again and wondered how this information leakage could be utilized by an attacker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrating the Future of Command and Control with Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://daniel-infosec.github.io/blog/wikipediac2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daniel-infosec.github.io/blog/wikipediac2/</guid>
      <description>This tool demonstrates what I believe will be the future of Command and Control (C2) for Red Teams and potentially Advanced Persistent Threats (APTs). With Domain Fronting slowly being killed by major CDNs and security teams getting better at looking for unusual sites (I still love that detection for new sites encrypted with LetsEncrypt certificates), Red Teams will look for alternate ways to hide their traffic. What better way than to utilize features of common sites that users are visiting anyways?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>